Where did you
bring me this time?
You talk too much.
Welcome to your new home.
- We’re sharing this?
- Obviously.
We're married.
You know what, maybe
you should just sleep.
Oh, okay.
Hey, woman!
What are you doing there?
Stop bothering me.
You better get used
to this kind of life...
wife.
Why is he lying next to me?
Isn’t this my bed?
Is he sleeping here too?
What is wrong with you?
Why are you yelling?
Why are you taking
your clothes off?
It's hot!
Then why are you
getting closer to me?
Idiot!
You're sitting on this.
Is Roswell really
my last name now?
- Happy Valentine’s Day, Moo!
- Is this really mine?
Thank you!
You’re so cute!
Damn it!
Zeke?
Where have you been?
Oh, hey.
Amiel?
So...
You gave this dog a name that's
close to your guy best friend's name.
And you just gave this cat that I
gifted you a random fucking name?
What the fuck is an Amiel?
It would've been
better if it was...
Kiel or...
I-
I don't know. You know what?
Whatever. Do whatever you want.
Amiel is a combination
of our names.
Because, right, Aemie
plus Ezekiel equals Amiel?
That was smart, right?
I came up with that.
Don’t you like it, Zeke?
I thought you’d like it.
I thought it would
make you happy.
Because isn’t it cute how I
combined my name and yours?
Fine, I’ll just think
of something else.
No.
I like Amiel.
Amiel.
Boss!
Boss! I caught the--
Shall we go, Mr. Roswell?
I'll just get my keys.
Okay.
There you are, Aemie.
So how was your
honeymoon with Mr. Roswell?
Honeymoon?
We don’t have that.
Not yet? Oh no, that won’t do.
You two need to
go on a honeymoon.
That’s just how
Mr. Roswell is, huh?
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Where are you going?
What, are you a doctor?
It’s already late and
you’re still going out?
What?
- Can I come?
- No, you stay here.
Let's go, Lamperouge.
- Hurry up!
- Bye, Aemie.
Just ask him about your
honeymoon later, okay?
You can do it. Goodluck!
Boss!
Honeymoon?
I’m gonna search honeymoon later.
- What are you staring at?
- Why?
Is it bad to look?
You’re ugly.
You look just like your boss.
You’re uglier.
I’m handsome.
Wow, I’m more handsome than you.
And I got here before you.
Yeah, you got here first.
You’re still broke.
Wow, you really
want to get hurt, huh?
Pssst, hey! Can you
two be quiet over there?
You’re so loud.
I’m trying to concentrate here.
I’m thinking about something.
What do people do
on a honeymoon?
What are the...
What is this?
Wow! It’s so pretty.
Oh, these flowers
are so beautiful!
I’ve only seen flowers
this nice in movies.
So pretty!
Does Zeke have a
flower shop business?
Hmm, probably not.
He doesn’t look like someone
who owns a flower shop.
Oh my god!
Aren’t these the kind people
give to someone they’re courting,
or to their girlfriend?
Oh my god!
Are these for me?
Wait, maybe I’m
assuming too much.
What if these aren’t for me?
Then who are they for?
If not for me?
Oh no...
Zeke is courting someone else!
He’s courting Kaizer!
Maybe that’s why they went
out earlier for a dinner date!
Oh my god!
Guys!
Guys, what do I do?
Oh my god!
I’m right, aren’t I?
I’m right, right?
I’m the wife, I should
be the one getting dated!
Oh my god!
Ah, yeah. Yeah!
You’re right, you’re right.
This honeymoon
really has to happen.
Because if this
honeymoon happens,
he will never ever fall
in love with another man.
Steady pressure,
keeps the sights aligned
and the shot on target.
If the enemy's in front,
don't fucking hold back.
Boss.
Is that him?
Yes, boss.
We’re here, baby Eisz.
Thank you, Mister.
Aemie.
Lamperouge.
I have a job for you.
But do this quietly.
Everyone listen.
Half the team inside,
the other half outside.
We’re sweeping every
room in boss’s house.
Mr. Roswell is sure
he hasn’t left yet.
If you find the target,
do not kill him.
We need him alive
for interrogation.
The rest of you
spread out for lookout.
But please...
be quiet.
Be calculated.
And remember,
Mrs. Roswell must not
know what’s happening.
So no noise.
Copy?
- Let’s go.
- Do you know what time it is?
I’m talking to you.
You’re there.
I thought you were a ghost.
I don’t know.
You don’t know?
Why can’t you figure it out?
Huh?
Zeke, sorry, my phone died.
I really didn’t know.
Just like you and Kaizer, right?
Who the fuck said
Lamperouge is my best friend?
Isn’t he?
The cat!
- What is it?
- It said talk to him.
Amiel.
Boss!
Boss! I caught the--
Shall we go, Mr. Roswell?
Tell us everything you know.
You can die trying!
But I won’t say anything!
You won’t learn
anything from me!
Talk, or this bullet
goes through your head.
No matter how much
you try to force me,
you will never know,
you can't stop us
from killing your wife!
You can die trying!
But I won’t say anything!
Damn...
You take care of
cleaning this mess.
Lamperouge!
We need more security
at the office and at home.
I don’t want Aemie
getting dragged into this.
I don’t want what happened
before to happen again.
Thank you, Mom, for
the toys you bought me.
Do you like them?
Yes, Mom.
Of course.
Anything for you, Ezekiel.
Thank you, Mom.
I love you so much, Mom.
I love you too, so, so, so much!
You, where did you come from?
You’re sweating all over.
We were just
playing at the court.
There.
Mommy?
Mommy!
Help!
Help, my Mommy!
Mommy!
Help!
Help! Mommy!
Mommy.
Oh, niece!
Why are you home so late?
Did you have dinner?
Yes, Auntie.
Auntie, is cuz here?
Huh?
Did she text you?
Why? Is she coming
back here again?
What is wrong with that kid?
I already sent her home earlier.
Auntie, what are
you talking about?
What do you mean sent her home,
this is where she comes
home to, here with us.
Huh?
What am I saying?
Auntie, about Aemie,
why isn’t she back yet?
Oh, that?
No, because she came here earlier,
then I sent her away again.
Huh? Auntie, why did
you send her away?
Well, because I wanted her to
have quality time with her husband.
What? Quality time?
With her husband?
Yes, I was just
about to tell you.
Sit down.
Aren’t you the handsome guy who
brought Baby Ae home the other day?
Sit, sit, sit.
Oh, wait, I’ll make
you something to drink.
What do you want?
Orange juice?
Grapes?
Oh, pineapple juice.
I'm sure it's a bit sour.
Wait.
Oh no,
sorry.
We ran out of pineapple juice.
But here, water.
Oh, I’ll just add
a little vinegar.
So it’ll be sour.
Here, drink.
I’m fine, Madam.
Sure?
Wait,
what brings you here anyway?
I wanted to ask for
your daughter’s hand.
Why are you asking me?
What?
You should,
ask Baby Ae for her hand.
I don't have it.
Wait.
Why do you want to take
my daughter’s hand anyway?
Madam...
I want to marry your daughter.
Marry?
Like get married?
I knew it!
I knew you and Baby Ae
had something going on.
Oh, wait, when’s the wedding?
So I can have my costume made.
Isn’t this exciting?
Auntie,
Auntie, come on.
There she goes again.
Auntie, why did you let her?
Oh my god.
For christ's sake, auntie.
Ah, so that’s how it is.
The place should be exciting.
Then it should be memorable.
Then there should
be quality time.
Then it should be...
fun.
What do people do
on a honeymoon?
Oh, why are you still awake?
Oh, you’re here already.
That was quick.
What?
What's with the staring?
Are you okay, Zeke?
Why does it feel like...
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
You seem deep in thought.
Yes, I'm sure.
Okay.
Oh, Zeke.
Oh right.
Is this for me?
Obviously, who
else would it be for?
I thought it was from
the person courting you.
Suitor?
Why would someone
be courting me?
Nothing, just maybe.
Yeah, right. Still pretending
like no one is courting him.
Look, he’s blushing.
I should actually be mad
because someone’s courting him.
But no, I should...
tell him about the honeymoon
first while he's still awake.
Oh, Zeke, wait.
Hey, Zeke. Coffee.
Why?
Why are you looking at me?
What now?
It’s just that, Zeke. I...
I just wanted to ask something.
What?
When are we going
on our honeymoon?
Hey!
Shit!
What happened?
Wait.
Do you want me to make
you another one instead?
It was fine too.
What the hell, I got wet
because of your nonsense.
Hey, wait.
Answer my question first.
Why aren’t we going
on a honeymoon?
Isn’t that what newlyweds do?
People who get married
go on honeymoons, right?
So why us?
We just got married too.
Why don’t we have that?
And they said it’s fun too.
I wanted to experience it too.
What?
You mean now?
Are you drunk? Why
are your cheeks so red?
You know what, just go to sleep.
Hey! Hey, Zeke, wait!
That’s so unfair.
You still haven’t
answered my question.
I still have so many questions.
Like, why did we get married?
Why didn’t I even get to wear a
wedding gown at our wedding?
There wasn’t even a wedding
cake, not even a reception,
not even those giveaways.
And then,
you’re too much.
All I'm asking for is a honeymoon,
but you can't even give me that?
You know, I didn’t even
get my dream wedding.
The... the motif, with dolls,
and then the cake.
Do you even know
what you’re saying?
Oh, there. I did my research.
Look.
And that's okay with you?
Of course. What kind
of question is that, Zeke?
Of course.
Are you even aware of
what you're asking for?
Yes.
Okay.
Okay. Honeymoon.
Zeke, just wait!
What now?
I thought you wanted
a honeymoon?
I do, but why?
You’re way too close.
What do you really want?
I want you to help
me think of a place
that would be nice to go to.
But why are you getting
close to me like that?
Because they said online it
should be fun and exciting.
Let's go to Boracay then. Okay.
Boracay feels
kind of far though.
And I’ve never been to Boracay,
so I don’t know
if it’s fun there.
Brazil.
Brazil!
Wow, another country.
Oh, I kind of like that.
But it’s so far.
I’ve never been there.
I don't know if it's fun there.
Then you think of it yourself.
You’re the one who
wants this, right?
That’s true, guys.
Where would be
a nice place to go?
It has to be exciting.
Fun too.
Where could it be?
Send help, please?
And send it to 23**.
I got it!
Zeke, I got it! I got it!
I know where we’re going!
- Where?
- I’m excited already.
To the amusement park!
Hey.
Hey, Zeke!
Are you okay?
This tastes good though.
You’re asking me
why I’m cooking?
Of course, I’m the wife.
It’s only right that
I serve my husband. Right?
And besides,
this is one of the ways
to be a perfect wife.
So Zeke won't get stolen from me,
and so our honeymoon happens,
I did my research. How do
you become a perfect wife?
Look at this, guys.
There’s a lot, right?
I have to do all of that.
It has to be balanced.
He’s really so handsome.
Oh...
Good morning, Zeke!
I’m leaving.
Hey, wait! Eat first!
Hey, eat first!
What a waste,
I prepared all this.
Who told you to cook?
Just eat already.
This is good.
Can’t you see this?
See? There’s so much.
There!
Doesn’t it look delicious?
Look at this,
I made an effort for you.
You should eat a lot.
Just looking at it
makes it look so good.
I don’t want that.
You don’t want that?
I got it.
Here, Zeke.
I already got all the...
things you can drink.
I don’t want any of those.
Oh, you don’t want these either?
I got it.
Wait, okay, wait, wait.
Baby Amiel,
let me have some,
okay? Just a little.
Why...
Why are you taking
Baby Amiel’s milk?
Don’t tell me you’re
making me drink that.
I thought you’d like this, Zeke.
That’s cat milk.
You’re making me drink that?
What about Baby Eisz’s,
would you like that?
So early in the morning
and you’re already mad.
I want coffee.
- Really?
- Yes.
Aye, aye, Captain!
Coffee, coffee, coffee.
He wants coffee.
We’re giving him coffee.
Then let’s add a little sugar.
- Just a little.
- You’re so slow.
Wait, why don’t
you just eat first
while I make it?
Here.
Here’s your coffee.
There.
You’re turning red, Zeke.
What? No.
I'm not.
Do you have a fever?
Can you not?
No.
Oh no! You’re turning even redder!
So red.
Stop it.
You’re blushing.
- No.
- There, look.
Oh my god.
Zeke, you’re blushing!
- Stop it.
- You are blushing.
Oh no, are you flustered?
Stop it.
- You’re in love, aren’t you?
- Will you shut up?
Touch the color red!
- I'm leaving.
- Hey, wait.
Zeke!
Oh no.
Is he pissed?
Are you sure Aemie’s husband
is really Mr. Ezekiel Roswell?
Isn’t he a multibillionaire?
- Do I look like I’m joking?
- Wait.
How did that happen? What was it?
Did she get scammed?
Hypnotized?
What if we go to his house?
If only I knew where they lived,
I would’ve gone there last night
so I could’ve pulled
cuz’s hair myself.
We’re going to Roswell Corp.
Your lunch, Mr. Roswell.
Hi, Zeke!
What?
What are you doing here?
I just brought you lunch.
Look,
Mr. Roswell already
has lunch so...
he won’t be eating that.
- Because...
- No.
He already has food.
Did Mr. Roswell tell
you to bring food, huh?
Acting like the secretary, girl?
Alright, Zeke.
I’ll just go home then.
Wait.
Did I say I wasn’t eating that?
Sir, what about your lunch?
Eat it. Or throw it. Whatever.
You may now leave, Kate.
Okay, sir.
Just go.
- Tada!
- Did you cook that?
Yeah, I really cooked this.
I studied under Mr. Boogle.
Mr. Boogle?
There.
Open it, hurry.
Taste it.
- Is it good, Zeke?
- No.
Too salty.
Really?
But you’ve already
taken several bites.
At least be quiet.
I’m eating, aren’t I?
You’re so harsh.
Hey!
Cuz?
What the fuck?
What are you doing here?
Mr. Roswell.
Let's talk.
Zeke, Zeke, Zeke.
Please don’t leave me here.
Look at my cousin’s face.
She’s so mad.
Please.
I'll be fast.
Hello, guys!
I missed you.
Annyeonghaseyo.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t tell you—
Congrats!
Oh my god.
Your husband is so handsome.
Yeah, right?
And he's so rich, girl.
You hit the jackpot.
Congrats, girl!
Congrats, Cuz!
What's up with you guys?
Cuz.
Come on, go ahead!
Slap me, pull my hair,
say all the bad words,
it’s okay.
You, crazy girl.
Of course I’m mad at you.
I was worried.
You didn’t even text me,
you didn’t even say anything.
Then I had to hear from my
Auntie that you got married?
What do you think
I am to you, Cuz?
Others?
You didn’t even invite
me to your wedding.
Cuz, who wouldn’t
get mad over that?
Cuz, I’m sorry.
I really was going to tell you.
Tell all of you.
Because of course, I was
building up to it because,
you know, it's complicated.
It's complicated.
Oh, what about school?
Of course I’m not stopping.
That’s not happening.
I’m still continuing.
You really are crazy.
Fine.
Congrats, Cuz.
You’re not mad anymore?
Not anymore.
But you’re still crazy, okay?
They’re okay now.
They’re about to hug now.
Fine. Alright then.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, Aemie. There’s
something I want to know.
What is it?
How was your honeymoon
with Mr. Roswell?
You really are shameless, Wakwak.
That dirty mind of yours.
Come on, Momo, I
didn’t even say anything.
Why, what’s wrong
with a honeymoon?
That’s fine, right?
Huh?
So you two already
went on a honeymoon?
Not yet.
We’re doing it on Saturday.
Where are you doing it?
- US?
- Japan? Bora?
No.
At the amusement park!
Her husband really got
the short end of the stick.
At the amusement park!
- This is nothing.
- You people are so confusing.
That sounds fine though.
Amusement park.
Moo, how are you?
Let's go. We still have class.
Okay, okay.
I think we should go.
I still have reports to submit.
We’re leaving now, Moo.
Wait, what happened?
Nothing.
We settled things.
But,
we reached an understanding now.
Okay.
Alright, let’s go.
Bye-bye, Cuz.
- Bye.
- Bye, Cuz.
- Bye, Mr. Roswell.
Settled things?
Hey, Zeke.
What did you and Moo talk about?
You don't need to know.
Oh my god.
They reached an understanding?
So, they're together now?
What about me now?
How?
There should be a
lot so it tastes better.
There! So nice!
More chocolate.
Perfect.
Cook for him.
Check.
Be sweet all the time
including sweet endearments.
I think I’m already
doing that now.
Oh, here it is.
There.
Wow.
Smells so good.
Perfect.
I think this is Zeke now.
Zeke!
Hi, Zeke!
Oh, I’ll take that.
What took you so long?
So grumpy.
How was work?
Woman, I’m hungry.
What are we having?
Perfect timing, I prepared
something for you.
- Come here.
- Oops.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
Don’t take it off.
What is that now?
Just because.
Look?
There, just stay
like that, stay there.
Hey, dude, that’s enough, dude.
- You might overdo it.
- Damn. I said don’t...
stop me.
Let him be for now, bro.
What do you mean let him be?
What if he overdoes it?
Bro, this is on us.
Then what can we even do?
He won’t let us stop him.
We all know Nico has been in
love with Aemie for a long time.
Let him grieve for now.
This is the first time
Nico ever liked a girl,
but it’s someone he can’t have.
Where are you going?
Hey, bro, where are you going?
- Leave me alone.
- What now?
- What are you planning?
- Stay here, dude. You’re drunk already.
- Sit down, sit down.
- What are you planning to do?
I’m going to kill myself!
- What did you say?
- Why?
You guys coming with me?
Bro, enough, bro!
Huh?
Bro, what is this?
You’re drunk, dude.
Wait.
Feels like we need backup.
Feels like it. Okay.
Make the call.
Sit here.
There.
Why do we even need blindfolds?
Wait, wait. Here it is.
One, two, three.
Surprise!
What is this?
Oh, see?
Number one and two
are already checked.
Don’t you know that, Zeke?
There, Zeke, that’s called cake.
Then those are marshmallows.
Then those are cupcakes.
Then there, that
one’s my favorite.
Shut the fuck up!
What am I supposed
to do with those?
- Huh?
- Zeke.
Of course, eat them.
That’s all your dinner.
Finish all of it, okay?
Finish all of it?
What do you want
to happen to me?
Get diabetes?
Isn’t there...
anything not sweet?
Come on, Zeke.
I prepared all of that for you.
Do you know? I baked all of that.
Then the chocolates, the
marshmallows, the gummies.
Everything, everything there.
Those, there, the ice cream.
All of those, I bought
with my savings.
Aren’t you...
aren’t you touched
by how sweet I am?
No.
What the heck!
Total fail.
But no.
I need to force Zeke to eat
so I can check number two.
Fighting!
Oh, okay, Zeke.
Then this one, cupcake.
- This is good.
- You, you eat that.
Eat— Eat all of it.
I made all of these for you.
It’s all yours.
No.
Oh, okay. Then the cake instead.
I don’t want it.
I got it.
How about yema?
I’ll make you some.
Or leche flan.
I don’t want it!
Hey. Zeke.
Let’s take a shot, asshole.
- Nico.
- Babe! Louie!
- Bro, just sit down.
- Stop him!
- Nico!
- Damn you.
Girl, what if we call Aemie?
Didn’t Louie say that
after we came from
Aemie’s husband’s company,
Nico became like this?
Zeke!
I’m telling you, you’re
really gonna get hungry
waiting there for
the food you ordered.
I don’t care.
Well, I don't know. Do you
think it's a good idea, girl?
I don't know, but we
should at least try it.
Ugh.
Zeke.
Venice.
- Hello? Venice?
- Aemie?
Girl, Nico is in trouble.
Huh?
Moo?
Why? What happened?
Just come here, girl.
Right now?
Wait, it’s just...
I'll send you the location.
Just come here, okay?
I really can’t.
Aemie, Nico's gonna die!
Girl, you're so mean.
Why would you say that?
If I didn’t say that to Aemie,
then Nico might really
die from all the drinking.
Hello?
Venice?
Moo is going to die
because of me?
Is it because my
husband is his boyfriend?
Is it because he’s
jealous of me and Zeke?
I need to go to him.
What happened?
Hey, girl!
I’m talking to you.
Huh?
It’s just that, Zeke...
Can I go out?
No.
Come on, Zeke, just for a bit.
I’ll come right back, promise.
Tell me first why.
It’s just... I’ll explain later.
Want me to bring you something?
- What do you want?
- No.
You stay here.
Why can’t I go?
Moo is going to die
because of me!
Whatever it is, Zeke,
I really have to go.
I’ll go with you.
I knew it.
When it comes to Moo,
he gets so eager.
No, no need.
I got it.
- I’ll go with you.
- Hey, yo! What's up, yo?
The fuck are you doing
here, Lamperouge?
- Hi, Kaizer.
- Just relax, Mr. Roswell.
I’m just visiting.
Hi, Aemie!
Wow, looking good.
Where are you two going?
Out!
- Me?
- Okay.
Come on. Come on.
Excuse us, boss.
The fuck?
Ow, Zeke!
Well, weren’t you going to let me
go as long as Kaizer came with me?
There’s a difference between
accompany and slithering around.
Slithering around?
But aren’t snakes the
ones who slither around?
What are we? Snakes?
Your imagination
is really weird, Zeke.
Don’t worry, Mr. Roswell.
I’m scared of you.
Okay?
Aemie, shall we?
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
- Bye.
It’s just ten minutes away.
- Thank you Kaizer!
- It’s okay.
Please tell Zeke
I’ll be home soon too.
No problem.
Bye. Take care.
Take care, Aemie.
Bye!
- Where's Moo?
- Good thing you made it!
- Oh my god.
- There’s Nico, getting drunk.
He's fighting with
all the boys he sees.
Bro, what is this? Enough.
Where’s the broth?
- Hey, Nico!
- This is a club.
Not a pares stand.
Nico, that’s enough.
You idiot.
Hey, why are you pulling me?
- There’s no broth.
- Shut up!
And you know what, girl?
He started drinking after we left
your husband’s company.
And I think it’s because of
what they talked about outside.
This is my fault.
I need to apologize to Moo!
He only falls in love once in a while,
and it had to be with my husband.
But wait.
Zeke is mine, right?
Because I’m the wife.
I’m sure
there are still other
men for Moo, right?
- Let's go.
- Let’s go to them.
- Come on.
- You keep grabbing me.
Touch me one more time
and I’ll punch you.
You’re being annoying,
we’re drinking here.
- Oh, what?
- Why is it so hot—
Moo!
Moo.
Aemie.
We’ll leave you
two alone for now.
We’ll wait outside.
- Bye, Aemie.
- Bye.
I'm sorry.
Moo?
Moo, are you hungry?
You didn’t eat dinner, did you?
Come on, let’s eat.
Don’t stand up.
You still can’t handle it.
No, I’m okay, Moo.
But you, you’re hungry, right?
Don’t worry about me, I’m okay.
Speaking of dinner.
[Hi, Zeke, Eat there already, okay?
[Finish everything I prepared, okay?]
[No!]
[Come on, Zeke! I thought
you were already hungry?]
[You haven’t had dinner yet, right?
Just finish all of that.]
[You need to eat that
so I can be a perfect wife.]
- Moo?
- Oh?
What do you want to eat?
Come on, let’s order.
I don’t like seeing you hungry.
Just spaghetti, Moo.
Wait, okay? Wait.
[Perfect wife? What time
are you coming home?]
Did I say perfect wife?
I did.
Oh no...
[Why are you taking
so long to reply???]
[Hey, woman! Are you
with your bestfriend?]
I really shouldn’t have
texted Zeke. He’s so annoying!
Should I tell him I’m with Moo?
I don’t want to.
[I'm not with Moo, Zeke.]
[I’m here with Venice. I’ll just
text when I’m heading home.]
[Eat there already, okay?]
Damn it!
The fuck are you looking at?
Boss, I heard something.
Spill it.
Wallace and Jerson are planning
to team up with your mortal
enemy to bring you down.
Okay.
Do you want it?
Just one.
Sir, that’s not my order.
You said you wanted spaghetti.
Oh, did I say that?
That looks good, Moo!
Eat now, Moo.
Okay, okay, okay.
- Moo?
- What?
Do you really love
Ezekiel Roswell?
Oh my god!
If I tell Moo I don’t love Zeke,
will he steal Zeke from me?
That can’t happen.
Our honeymoon hasn’t
even happened yet.
Then he’ll steal him from me.
And I need to fight for
my rights as the wife.
Right.
Come on, Moo! Of course.
I love him so much.
Hey, Moo.
Sorry, Moo.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
It’s okay.
I've accepted it.
If there’s really anything
I can do for you, Moo...
What if I set Moo
up with Kaizer?
Moo, I’m going to
the restroom first.
Uhh. Ah, okay.
Don’t touch it.
That’s mine, okay?
- Even just a little?
- It’s mine!
Oh, Moo.
You missed a call.
Huh? Really? Who?
Your husband.
Let's go.
Let's go before he sees us.
- He might get the wrong idea.
- Okay.
Okay, okay.
Wait.
Are they planning to elope?
Okay.
Wait, wait.
You're still tipsy, hold on.
Come here.
Thank you.
Okay.
Aemie.
Zeke. What are you doing here?
Let's go.
Why are you screaming?
Zeke, you finished all the sweets!
Talking about diabetes and all that,
but you still ate it anyway.
Hello, Tutti!
Who the fuck is Tutti?
Are you talking to
some random douche?
No, Zeke! You're Tutti.
And I'm Frutti.
Aemie, do you have class today?
Nope.
But I'm looking for Dodong.
Dodong?
Yeah, my husband.
Zeke.
Isn't my pet name
for him cute or what?
My love!
What the hell are you
shouting that word for?
Come on, Zeke.
We should have an endearment.
I'm flying to Hawaii.
While I'm gone, I want you
to handle the whole company.
My hands are too small to
handle a whole company.
Oh!
I am the acting CEO!
And I'm the best actress.
MkvDrama.net